<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog on Radu Ciurca</title>
    <link>https://raduciurca.com/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog on Radu Ciurca</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://raduciurca.com/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Willpower is for suckers</title>
      <link>https://raduciurca.com/blog/willpower/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://raduciurca.com/blog/willpower/</guid>
      <description>Image source John set himself a goal of working out daily on a Sunday. He started going to the gym on Monday. This was 3 years ago. He has been going to the gym ever since. He hasn&amp;rsquo;t had a problem with motivation whatsoever. He hasn&amp;rsquo;t missed a day. You know why? Because he&amp;rsquo;s got willpower.
You know what else John is? An imaginary character. He doesn&amp;rsquo;t exist. Nobody has it easy like that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You&#39;re underestimating the amount of stupidity around you</title>
      <link>https://raduciurca.com/blog/stupidity/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://raduciurca.com/blog/stupidity/</guid>
      <description>First, we need to define what a stupid person is. In his short book &amp;lsquo;The Basic Laws of Human Stupidity&amp;rsquo;, Carlo Cipolla describes a stupid person as follows:
 A stupid person is a person who causes losses to another person or to a group of persons while himself deriving no gain and even possibly incurring losses.
 You might think, &amp;lsquo;wait a second that doesn&amp;rsquo;t make any sense, why would anyone cause a loss, while they gain absolutely nothing in return&amp;rsquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quotes</title>
      <link>https://raduciurca.com/blog/quotes/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://raduciurca.com/blog/quotes/</guid>
      <description>This is a list of quotes (and some notes) that I&amp;rsquo;m constantly updating, taken from different things that I’ve read, listened or watched. I believe that a quote gives you an insight into how and what that particular person thinks.
If a quote doesn’t necessarily have an author or if it’s a common saying I’ll put VA besides it (Various Authors). If you see a quote that you know for a fact has a certain author, you can let me know on Twitter @raduciurca.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>